motorsportretro.com 2018-12-18

# Privacy Policy - Motorsport Retro

[Home](http://www.motorsportretro.com/) » Privacy Policy

## Privacy Policy

  1. **How is personal information collected?**  
In order to provide a quality service, motorsportretro.com (us/we) offers customers the ability to subscribe to our newsletters, enter competitions and promotions through [http://www.motorsportretro.com](http://www.motorsportretro.com/). In order to provide these services, motorsportretro.com collects personal information about customers. Collection of this information will occur at the time you enter a competition or subscribe to the newsletter.
  2. **What personal information does motorsportretro.com collect and why?**  
We may collect your name, address, email address and telephone number(s) in order to send you the communications you’ve requested or to send you a prize. Even if you initially choose to subscribe to receive communications from us, you may also unsubscribe or resubscribe at a later stage at [http://www.motorsportretro.com](http://www.motorsportretro.com/)
  3. **Will personal information be given to anyone else?**  
motorsportretro.com will only disclose information about you if you have given your prior consent, so that you can be provided with promotional material and special offers that you have requested. Otherwise, motorsportretro.com will only disclose personal information if this is required by law or permitted under the Privacy Act.
  4. **Security of personal information**  
motorsportretro.com protects the personal information it collects in a secure database. Any employees with access to this database are required, as a condition of their employment, to treat personal information held by motorsportretro.com as confidential, and to maintain the confidentiality of that personal information at all times.
  5. **Access and correction**  
Under the Privacy Act, you have a right to seek access to information that motorsportretro.com holds about you. You also have the right to ask us to correct information about you, which is inaccurate, incomplete or out of date. If you wish to access the personal information that we hold about you, a request can be lodged using the contact details provided in point 9 (below).
  6. **Online collection of personal and non-personal information**  
For each visitor to our website, our server automatically recognises and stores the visitor’s IP address. In addition, our website uses cookies. Most web browsers are set by default to accept cookies. However, if you do not wish to receive any cookies you may set your browser to either prompt or refuse cookies. Please note that rejecting cookies will restrict the functionality of the website as a whole. We also use cookies for tracking the statistics of our website. This allows us to better understand our users and improve the layout and functionality of our website.
  7. **Online disclosures**  
To try and bring you offers that are of interest to you, motorsportretro.com has relationships with other companies that we allow to place advertisements on our web pages. If you visit our website, advertisement server companies may collect information such as your IP address and clickstream information.
  8. **Links to other websites**  
Sometimes our website contains links to third party websites, for your convenience and information. When you access a non-motorsportretro.com website, please understand that motorsportretro.com is not responsible for the privacy practices of that site. We suggest that you review the privacy policies of each site you visit.
  9. **Additional privacy information and how to contact motorsportretro.com**  
motorsportretro.com may change its Privacy Policy at any time. motorsportretro.com will make available this policy to anyone who requests it. For further information about privacy issues and the protection of privacy visit the Australian Federal Privacy Commissioner’s website at www.privacy.gov.au. If you feel that motorsportretro.com is not complying with this Privacy Policy, or if you have other privacy concerns, please contact us:

  * by submitting an email [Support Request](http://www.motorsportretro.com/contact/)
  * by letter to Motorsport Retro, PO Box 3251, Bellevue Hill, NSW 2023, AUSTRALIA
